# Isaac Pereira, Customer Support

Mérida, Venezuela, +58 4162572870, isaac.pereira.50159@gmail.com

**LINKS** 

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/isaac-pereira-271a66285

# **Profile**

Experienced customer service agent with background in handling interactions in Spanish and English and a passion for providing excellent customer support. Strong skills in active listening, interpersonal interactions, and empathy combined with technical proficiency in CRM systems and front- end development, combined with experience in administrative support roles.

#### **Experience**

### **April 2022 – November 2022 Administrative Assistant**

- Assist in organizing community events and activities.
- Managed communication with event participants and activities.
- Provided administrative support, including data entry and filling.
- Demonstrated strong organizational skills and attention to detail.

#### Jan 2024 – Jun 2024 Customer Support Agent Delivery Company:

- Used customer service software to track customer interactions and order status.
- Developed and implement customer service strategies to improve customer satisfaction.
- Analyzed customer feedback to improve customer services process and policies.
- Contributed to team success by integrating interpersonal skills and fostering a positive work environment.
- Organize, renew change and create AI templates for quick responses to the most common customer questions and be able to provide a quick response and address customer concerns and problems more quickly.

#### Education

### Oct 2008 – Jul 2013 High School, Nuestra señora del Rosario

Graduated with a strong focus on scientific studies, proficiency and IT and computing skills.

#### Jul 2022 CEVAM

Enhanced written and spoken English skills through comprehensive coursework and practical exercises.

### **Skills**

- Proficient in CRM systems for customer relationship management.
- Front-End development skills, including building CRUD applications and interactive web pages.
- Active Listening: Attentively engaged with customers to understand their needs and concerns.
- Interpersonal Interactions: Fostered positive interactions within teams and with clients.
- Empathy: Demonstrated understanding and care for customer perspectives.
- Problem-Solving: Quickly addressed and resolved customer issues.
- Cultural Tolerance: Exhibited respect and understanding for diverse cultural backgrounds.